



# **Summary**

I'm Pourya Dehghan a Software engineer with the background of petrochemical engineering educations and designing experience. I started my coding journey two years ago, I feel really lucky that my job is my biggest hobbies. I'm eager to make the leap and continue refining my skills with the right company.

### **Skills**

HTML, CSS, javaScript, React, python, Django,

MongoDB, Boostrap, PostrageSQL, Github, PhotoShop, Lightroom

# **Education and Training**

#### Some College

General Assembly Remote Software Engineer

#### Bachelor of Science

Marvdasht Azad University
Petrochemical Engineering, 2013

# **Experience**

#### General Assembly

Software Engineer | Remote 05/2021 to 08/2021

Learning programming and computer science fundamentals, and creating full stack applications.

#### Uber

Driver | Atlanta, GA 04/2017 to 06/2021

#### Yerce

Photo Editor & Designer 06/2014 to 12/2016

Photographer

Designing Wedding albums.

#### Languages

# English: Persian: Professional Native/ Bilingual Turkish: Limited

### Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://www.pouryadegan.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/degan90
- https://github.com/Degan90